Reza Khoirul Wijaya Putra

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

I'm 17 years old, and I was born and raised in Karawang, Indonesia. I graduated from a vocational high school, and my hobby is coding. I enjoy taking on freelance projects, and I have three years of experience as a programmer. I am interested in the backend developer position, but I am also proficient in full-stack development using Laravel.

Experience

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

2023 - NOW

- Currently I am a freelance web developer, specifically a fullstack web developer.
- As a professional working programmer, I write code neatly and use code refactoring.

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2020 - 2022

- I reinforced the basic fundamentals of programming by understanding the concepts.
- I started learning computational thinking.
- I started learning data structures and algorithms.
- During COVID, it made me more interested in learning basic programming.
- I started to create a project that directly integrates with SQL and NO SQL databases.

LEARNING BY DOING

2019

- I learned excel for developers and learned logic and coding from Visual Basic Application programming.
- I learned conditioning, looping, algorithms, validation.

Certifications

- 1st place in the Karawang Regency LKS (Lomba Kompetensi Siswa) in website technology competition - 2022
- As a participant in the West Java Province LKS website technology competition - 2022
- 2nd place in the National of Muhammadiyah Vocational High School in website design competition - 2024

Education

SDN PURWASARI III

Elementary School 2013 - 2018

SMPN 1 PURWASARI

Junior High School 2018 - 2021

SMKS TI MUHAMMADIYAH CIKAMPEK

Vocational High School Majoring Software Engineering 2021 - 2024

Skills

HTML - CSS - JavaScript - TypeScript - Google API - PHP - Laravel - Express - WordPress - Bootstrap - Tailwind - React - MySQL - Basic Statistika - MongoDB - JQuery - VueJS - Teamwork - Git - GitHub - NodeJS - Linux - Clean Code - OOP - Critical Thinking - Good Communication - RESTful API - OAuth - Websocket - Ms. Excel - Ms. Word - Ms. PowerPoint

Projects

Web Absensi - Kasir berbasis VBA - Web PPDB Sekolah - Web Pelayanan Masyarakat - Web Kuis - Web Live Polling - WhatsApp BOT Quick Count - Web Game Breakout - Basic Statistic - Integration Payment Gateway Midtrans - REST API WhatsApp - Web Koperasi - Web PRB - Web TODO - RESTful API CRUD Layered Architecture - Web Perpus - Setup Ubuntu Server

Contact Information



+62 857 1414 8247



www.rezawp.my.id



rezaaawp@gmail.com